http://www.murach.com/privacy-policy

Murach Books
Murach For Instructors
My Cart (0)
My Account
Home
Shop BooksView AllWeb Design BooksWeb Development BooksPython and C++ BooksMobile Development BooksDatabase Programming BooksJava Programming BooksC# Programming BooksVisual Basic Programming BooksMainframe Programming BooksPrevious EditionsAbout Our eBookseBooks OverviewCustomer ServiceCustomer Service OverviewReturn Policy for Print Books and eBooksJoin Our Email ListOur International DistributorsHow to Place an International OrderMeet Our Customer Service StaffContact UsCourseware for TrainersCourseware for Trainers Overview3 Ways to Use Our Books for Training What Our Courseware IncludesHow to Prepare for a CourseHow to Order Our Books and CoursewareWhat Managers and Trainers Say About UsAbout UsAbout Us OverviewCompany HistoryWhat We Do DifferentlyWrite for Us?What Our Customers Say About UsContact UsBooks for College Instructors
My Account
Murach for Instructors Website
Customer Service 1-800-221-5528
Contact Us
Shop Books
View AllWeb Design BooksWeb Development BooksPython and C++ BooksMobile Development BooksDatabase Programming BooksJava Programming BooksC# Programming BooksVisual Basic Programming BooksMainframe Programming BooksPrevious Editions
About Our eBooks
eBooks Overview
Customer Service
Customer Service OverviewReturn Policy for Print Books and eBooksJoin Our Email ListOur International DistributorsHow to Place an International OrderMeet Our Customer Service StaffContact Us
Courseware for Trainers
Courseware for Trainers Overview3 Ways to Use Our Books for Training What Our Courseware IncludesHow to Prepare for a CourseHow to Order Our Books and CoursewareWhat Managers and Trainers Say About Us
About Us
About Us OverviewCompany HistoryWhat We Do DifferentlyWrite for Us?What Our Customers Say About UsContact UsBooks for College Instructors
Home / Privacy Policy
In brief, we don’t share the data that you provide for us...ever! But in case you’re interested, here are the details.
The personal data that we collect and save
We collect personal data (like name, email address, address, and phone number) and save it in our database in these cases:
When you place an order
When you create an account
When you download chapters or applications
When you join our email list
When you post a review for one of our books
We also keep a record of:
The items that you’ve bought
The items that you’ve returned
The items that you’ve downloaded
When you place an order, we also collect but do not save:
Credit card information
As soon as the order has been processed, the credit-card data is destroyed.
How we use the data that we collect
We only use the data that we collect in ways that we think will improve your experiences with us. That includes:
Processing and tracking your orders
Sending you information about special orders and promotions
Sending you updates about products you have purchased
With every email, you will have the chance to “unsubscribe” to future emails.
What data we share with others
We have never shared the information in our database with third-parties...ever...and see no reason to do so in the future.
The only exceptions, which have never happened, would be if we were required to do so by law or believed that an action was ethically necessary. For example, we might have to provide personal data:
To comply with a legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order.
Or to protect against the misuse or unauthorized use of our website.
How we secure your data
Our goal is to protect the data that we collect from you against loss, misuse, or alteration. To do that, we use a variety of technologies and practices. For instance:
When you make a purchase, create an account, or join our email list, your information is transmitted in a safe, encrypted format.
We maintain the data you provide, along with a record of your purchases, in a secure database.
We don’t save the credit card information that you provide for an order.
Occasionally, our website provides links to other websites that we think you might find useful.
Note, however, that these sites operate independently and have their own privacy and security policies, over which we have no control.
About our links to other sites
Occasionally, our website provides links to other websites that we think you might find useful.
Note, however, that these sites operate independently and have their own privacy and security policies, over which we have no control.
What about policy changes
If our privacy policy changes, which is unlikely, we will post the changes on our web site. That’s why you may want to periodically review our privacy policy.
Any questions or comments?
For questions, comments, or assistance, please contact us:
Mike Murach & Associates, Inc.4340 N. KnollFresno, CA  937221-800-221-5528 or 1-559-440-9071murachbooks@murach.com
College Instructors
If you’re a college instructor who would like to consider a book for a course, please visit our website for instructors to learn how to get a complimentary review copy and the full set of instructional materials.
What We Do Differently
The short answer to what we do that’s different from other publishing companies is: Just about everything. Learn what makes our books better
Our Ironclad Guarantee
You must be satisfied. Try our print books for 30 days or our eBooks for 14 days. If they aren't the best you've ever used, you can return the books or cancel the eBooks for a prompt refund.
No questions asked!
Contact Murach Books
For orders and customer service:
1-800-221-5528
Weekdays, 8 to 4 Pacific Time
murachbooks@murach.com
eMail Sign Up
Sign up today to receive special discounts, product alerts, and news from Murach Books.
Sign Up
College Instructors
If you're a college instructor who would like to consider a book for a course, please visit our website for instructors to learn how to get a complimentary review copy and the full set of instructional materials.
Shop Books
Web design books
Web development books
Database programming books
Python programming books
Java programming books
C# programming books
Visual Basic programming books
